Guide to the Radio Advertising Bureau Collection
University of Maryland Libraries
- Radio Advertising Bureau Collection, Airlines; 1954-1968; 1958-1964; 1958-1965; Mass Media and Culture Special Collections, University of Maryland Libraries, Hornbake Library, College Park, MD, 20742. Tel: 301-405-9212, Fax: 301-314-2634, Email: askhornbake@umd.edu; Radio Advertising Bureau; 3300 sound discs; 2013-3; The Radio Advertising Bureau (RAB) is a national radio advertising trade organization whose history dates back to 1950. To showcase radio's potential during the rise of the television era, the RAB began collecting examples of ads from all over the country beginning in 1954. Many of these ads were used in workshops and presentations, and by the mid-1960s the RAB had teamed with the Clio Awards in order to recognize the best of radio advertising each year. When the RAB moved from Dallas to New York, they donated the ads to the Broadcast Pioneers Library, which was accessioned by the University of Maryland Libraries in 1994.; 47 items
  This series contains advertisements for airlines. Series is arranged alphabetically by airline name.
- Amusement, 1958-1964; 16 items
  This series contains advertisements related to recreational activities.
  - Parks and Shows, 1961-64
    Subseries is alphabetized by name of organization.
  - Race Tracks, 1958-64
    Subseries is alphabetized by name of track.
  - Lodging, 1965
    Subseries is alphabetized by name of hotel.
  - Restaurants, 1963
    Subseries is alphabetized by name of restaurant.
  - Places to Go, 1961-64
    Subseries is alphabetized by name of destination.
- Apparel, 1958-65; 10 items
  This series contains advertisments for clothing and shoes.
  - Clothes, 1958-65
    Subseries is alphabetized by brand name.
  - Shoes, 1960-1965
- Automobiles/Auto Products, 1956-1965; 95 items
  This series contains advertisments for cars and related products.
  - Domestic, 1956-1966
    Subseries is alphabetized by company name.
  - Foreign, 1958-1965
  - Accessories, 1957-1963
  - Public Service Announcements, 1956-63
    Subseries is alphabetized by name of orgnaization.
  - Rentals, n/a
- Award-Winning Ads, 1964-67; 4 sets
  This series contains advertisements that were selected for awards, alphabetized by awarding institution.
- Financial, 1957-64; 32 items
  This series contains advertisements related to finance.
  - Banks, 1957-64
    Subseries is alphabetized by bank name.
  - Insurance, 1960-64
- Beer, 1956-1969; 97 items
  This series contains advertisements for beer, alphabetized by brand name.
- Cigarettes, Cigars and Tobacco, 1957-68; 64 items
  This series contains advertisements related to tobacco products, alphabetized by brand name.
- Drugs/Cosmetics, 1955-1966; 79 items
  This series contains advertisements related to pharmaceutical and cosmetic products.
  - Baby Products/Tissues, 1955-61
  - Cold Medicines, 1957-64
  - Deodorants, 1958-64
  - Men's Products, 1956-64
  - Suntan Lotion, 1959-63
  - Dental, 1956-66
  - Women's Products, 1957-64
  - Over-the-Counter Remedies, 1957-64
- Farm Products, 1958-63; 13 items
  This series contains advertisements related to farm equipment and products.
  - Machinery, 1958-63
  - Fertilizer, 1958-63
- Food, 1955-64; 194 items
  This series contains advertisments for food products, categorized by type.
  - Bread, 1957-63
  - Cakes & Cookies, 1956-63
  - Candy & Gum, 1957-63
  - Desserts, 1964
  - Snacks, 1958-63
  - Cereal, 1957-64
  - Coffee, 1955-64
  - Dairy, 1959-64
  - Fruits & Juices, 1960-65
  - Fish & Seafood, 1956-63
  - Meats, 1957-61
  - Processed Meat Products, 1957-65
  - Rice, Pasta & Sauces, 1958-63
  - Pet Food, 1958-61
  - Frozen Foods, 1958-65
  - Processed Foods, 1956-64
  - Condiments, 1957-63
  - Spices, 1960-65
  - Baking, 1958-64
- Household Products, 1959-63; 2 items
  This series contains advertisements for household products.
- Airlines, 1958-1965; 47 items
  - Allegheny Airlines, 1958, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1.0)
  - American Airlines, 1956, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
  - BOAC, 1957 (Folder 3.0)
  - Bonanza Airlines, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
  - Continental Airlines, 1962-63 (Folder 5.0)
  - Delta Airlines/Airways, 1958-59, 1961-62 (Folder 6.0)
  - Eastern Airlines, 1957-59 (Folder 7.0)
  - Iberia of Spain Airlines, 1965 (Folder 8.0)
  - Irish International Airlines, 1965 (Folder 9.0)
  - Japan Airlines, 1961-62, 1963 (Folder 10.0)
  - KLM Royal Dutch, 1958 (Folder 11.0)
  - National Airlines, 1958 (Folder 12.0)
  - North Central Airlines, 1963 (Folder 13.0)
  - Northwest Airlines, 1958 (Folder 14.0)
  - Northwest Orient Airlines, 1957, 1959, 1960, 1963 (Folder 15.0)
  - Ozark Airlines, 1963 (Folder 16.0)
  - Pacific Airlines, 1963 (Folder 17.0)
  - Pan American Airlines, 1958, 1963-64 (Folder 18.0)
  - Piedmont Airlines, 1957 (Folder 19.0)
  - PSA Airlines, 1958, 1963 (Folder 20.0)
  - Qantas Airlines, 1964 (Folder 21.0)
  - Sabena Airlines, undated (Folder 22.0)
  - Southern Airways/Airlines, 1963 (Folder 23.0)
  - Trans World Airways/Airlines, 1957, 1962-63 (Folder 24.0)
  - United Aircraft Corporation, 1958 (Folder 25.0)
  - United Airlines, 1957-58, 1963 (Folder 26.0)
  - Viasa International Airlines, 1961 (Folder 27.0)
  - Western Airlines, 1958 (Folder 28.0)
- Amusement, 1958-1964; 16 items
  - Parks and Shows, 1961-64
    - Freedomland Amusement Park, 1961, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1.0)
    - Ice Capades, undated (Folder 2.0)
    - Palisades Park, null (Folder 3.0)
  - Race Tracks, 1958-64
    - Aqueduct Race Track, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1.0)
    - Atlantic City Race Track, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
    - Bradywine Raceway, 1959 (Folder 3.0)
    - Hollywood Park Race Track, 1958 (Folder 4.0)
    - Roosevelt Raceway, 1964 (Folder 5.0)
  - Lodging, 1965
    - Hilton Hotels, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1.0)
  - Restaurants, 1963
    - Monmouth Park Jockey Club, undated (Box 5, Folder 1.0)
    - Schrafft's Restaurant, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
  - Places to Go, 1961-64
    - Brunswick Corporation (Bowling), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1.0)
    - Huntington Harbor, 1962 (Folder 2.0)
    - Owens Yacht, 1964 (Folder 3.0)
    - State of Minnesota, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
- Apparel, 1958-65; 10 items
  - Clothes, 1958-65
    - A-1 Slacks, featuring Jerry Lewis, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1.0)
    - Dickies Men's and Boy's Wear, 1958 (Folder 2.0)
    - H.I.S. Sportswear, 1963 (Folder 3.0)
    - Howard Clothes, 1960-61 (Folder 4.0)
  - Shoes, 1960-1965
    - National Shoes, 1960-63, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 1.0)
    - Thom McCann Shoes, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - U.S. Keds Shoes, 1961 (Folder 3.0)
- Automobiles/Auto Products, 1956-1965; 95 items
  - Domestic, 1956-1966
    - Buick, 1957, 1960-64 (Box 9, Folder 1.0)
    - Cadillac, 1960, 1964-66 (Folder 2.0)
    - Chevrolet/Chevy, 1967, 1960-65 (Folder 3.0)
    - Chrysler, 1957, 1961, 1966 (Folder 4.0)
    - Chrysler Valiant, 1959 (Folder 5.0)
    - Dodge, 1957-58, 1962, 1964, 1966 (Folder 6.0)
    - Edsel, 1959 (Folder 7.0)
    - Ford, 1957-59. 1963-65 (Folder 8.0)
    - Lincoln, 1963 (Folder 9.0)
    - Lincoln Mercury, 1960, 1963-64, 1966 (Folder 10.0)
    - Oldsmobile, 1963-64 (Folder 11.0)
    - Plymouth, 1957, 1959, 1963, 1966 (Folder 12.0)
    - Plymouth Suburban, 1957 (Folder 13.0)
    - Plymouth Torsion Aire, 1957 (Folder 14.0)
    - Plymouth Valiant, 1960-61 (Folder 15.0)
    - Pontiac, 1959-60, 1963, 1966 (Folder 16.0)
    - Rambler, 1956, 1959 (Folder 17.0)
    - Studebaker, 1960 (Folder 18.0)
    - Studebaker Lark, 1960 (Folder 19.0)
  - Foreign, 1958-1965
    - Citroen, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 1.0)
    - Hillman (Roote's Motors), 1958 (Folder 2.0)
    - Honda Motorcycle, 1965 (Folder 3.0)
    - Jaguar, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Opel (Buick-General Motors), 1963-64 (Folder 5.0)
    - Renault Gordini, 1961 (Folder 6.0)
    - Renault Caravelle, 1961 (Folder 7.0)
    - Renault Dauphine, 1961 (Folder 8.0)
    - Simca, 1960 (Folder 9.0)
    - Simca (pre-Chrysler), undated (Folder 10.0)
    - Triumph TR-3, 1961 (Folder 11.0)
    - Volkswagon, 1961, 1964 (Folder 12.0)
    - Volkswagon Karmann Ghia, 1964 (Folder 13.0)
    - Volvo, 1963 (Folder 14.0)
  - Accessories, 1957-1963
    - Alamite Kleen Treet, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 1.0)
    - Bardahl Tune-Ups, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - Champion Spark Plug Company, 1960 (Folder 3.0)
    - Chevron, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
    - Dupont Telar, 1960 (Folder 5.0)
    - Dupont Zerex and Zerone, 1957 (Folder 6.0)
    - Fram Oil Fitters, 1959-60 (Folder 7.0)
    - G.M Harrison 4-Season Climate Control, 1962 (Folder 8.0)
    - General Motors AC Spark Plugs, 1961-62 (Folder 9.0)
    - Goodyear Tires, 1961, 1963 (Folder 10.0)
    - Gulf Antifreeze and Summer Coolant, 1962 (Folder 11.0)
    - Gulf Power Crest Batteries, 1962 (Folder 12.0)
    - Gulf Tires, 1961, 1963 (Folder 13.0)
    - Rayco, 1957-58, 1961-63 (Folder 14.0)
    - Rayco Muffler, 1959 (Folder 15.0)
    - Rayco Shock Absorber, 1960 (Folder 16.0)
    - Rayco Tires, 1960 (Folder 17.0)
  - Public Service Announcements, 1956-63
    - Gasoline Tax Education Committee, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1.0)
    - GMAC, 1958 (Folder 2.0)
    - General Motors Guardian Maintenance, 1961-63 (Folder 3.0)
    - Gulf Safety Campaign, 1956 (Folder 4.0)
    - The Upholstery Leather A Group, Inc, undated (Folder 5.0)
  - Rentals, n/a
    - Econo-Car, undated (Box 13, Folder 1.0)
    - National Car Rental System, undated (Folder 2.0)
- Award-Winning Ads, 1964-67; 4 sets
  - Award-Winning Ads, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 1.0)
  - Clio Awards, 1967 (Folder 2.0)
  - Golden Record Plaque Winners, 1965 (Folder 3.0)
  - Radio Advertising Bureau Awards, 1964 (Folder 4.0)
- Financial, 1957-64; 32 items
  - Banks, 1957-64
    - American Bankers Association, feat. Eddie Bracken, undated (Box 15, Folder 1.0)
    - Bank of America, feat. Stan Freberg, 1958 (Folder 2.0)
    - Bank of America Bank Americard, 1959 (Folder 3.0)
    - Bank of America Timeplan Loans, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
    - Bank of America Travelers Cheques, 1964 (Folder 5.0)
    - Beneficial Finance, 1959-60 (Folder 6.0)
    - Citizens and Southern Bank, 1960 (Folder 7.0)
    - Community Loan Consolidation Company, 1957 (Folder 8.0)
    - Dime Savings of Brooklyn, undated (Folder 9.0)
    - First National Bank of Arizona, 1963 (Folder 10.0)
    - First National Bank of Oregon, 1958 (Folder 11.0)
    - First National City Bank, New York, 1960 (Folder 12.0)
    - GAC Finance Corporation, 1957 (Folder 13.0)
    - Household Finance Loan Corporations, 1958-60, 1962 (Folder 14.0)
    - Morris Plan Company of California, undated (Folder 15.0)
    - Northwestern National Bancorporation, 1958 (Folder 16.0)
    - Pacific Finance, 1960 (Folder 17.0)
    - Seaboard Finance Company, 1963 (Folder 18.0)
    - S.I.C., 1959-60 (Folder 19.0)
  - Insurance, 1960-64
    - Equitable Life Assurance Policy, 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 1.0)
    - General Insurance Company of America (Safeco Auto), 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - John Hancock, 1960-61 (Folder 3.0)
    - Liberty Mutual, 1960 (Folder 4.0)
    - Life of Georgia, 1962 (Folder 5.0)
    - Nationwide Auto Insurance, 1962 (Folder 6.0)
    - Northwestern National Life Insurance Company, 1960-61 (Folder 7.0)
- Beer, 1956-1969; 97 items
  - Adolph Coors Company, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1.0)
  - Aloca Can Beer Tops, undated (Folder 2.0)
  - Ambassador Beer, 1958 (Folder 3.0)
  - Ballantine Ale, 1957, 1962, 1964, 1967 (Folder 4.0)
  - Bavarian Brewing Company, 1959 (Folder 5.0)
  - Blatz Beer, 1957 (Folder 6.0)
  - Blitz Weinhard, 1958-59, 1963 (Folder 7.0)
  - Budweiser, 1957-58, 1960-65, 1967-69 (Folder 8.0)
  - Burgert Beer, 1963 (Folder 9.0)
  - Burgermeister Beer, 1959 (Folder 10.0)
  - Burgermeister Beer-Schlitz, 1958 (Folder 11.0)
  - Busch Bavarian Beer, 1962-63 (Folder 12.0)
  - Carlsburg, 1962-64 (Folder 13.0)
  - Champale, 1963 (Folder 14.0)
  - Country Club Malt Liquor, 1957 (Folder 15.0)
  - Drewry's Ltd, U.S.A. Inc, 1959 (Folder 16.0)
  - Fither's, 1961 (Folder 17.0)
  - Genessee Brewing Company, 1963 (Folder 18.0)
  - Goetz, 1958 (Folder 19.0)
  - Gold Bond Beer, 1959 (Folder 20.0)
  - Grain Belt, 1965 (Folder 21.0)
  - Grand Prize Beer, 1957 (Folder 22.0)
  - Gunther Beer, 1958-59 (Folder 23.0)
  - Theo Hamm Brewing Co. (Gunther Beer), 1963 (Folder 24.0)
  - Theo Hamm Brewing Co. (Hamm's St. Paul), 1961, 1963, 1965-66 (Folder 25.0)
  - Heidelberg Beer, 1958 (Folder 26.0)
  - G. Heidelberg Brewing Co. Old Style Beer, 1964 (Folder 27.0)
  - Iron City Beer, 1960 (Folder 28.0)
  - Jax Beer, 1961 (Folder 29.0)
  - Knickerbocker Beer, 1958-59, 1963 (Folder 30.0)
  - Lone Star Beer, 1963 (Folder 31.0)
  - Lucky Lager, 1963 (Folder 32.0)
  - Miller Highlife, 1958-59 (Folder 33.0)
  - Narragansett Brewing Company, 1958, 1962-63 (Folder 34.0)
  - Narragansett Beer, 1963 (Folder 35.0)
  - National Beer (National Brewing Company), 1963 (Folder 36.0)
  - Olde Frothingslosh, 1958 (Folder 37.0)
  - Olympia, 1957, 1960, 1965 (Folder 38.0)
  - Pabst Blue Ribbon Beer, 1957-59, 1962-63 (Folder 39.0)
  - Pfeiffer, 1957-58 (Folder 40.0)
  - Piels, feat. Bob and Ray, 1959-60, 1962-64 (Folder 41.0)
  - Rheingold Beer (Liebmann Breweries), 1956-58 (Folder 42.0)
  - Rheingold Beer (Rheingold Breweries), 1956 (Folder 43.0)
  - The F&M Schaeffer Brewing Company, 1957-59, 1963 (Folder 44.0)
  - Schlitz, 1957-58, 1961-63, 1965 (Folder 45.0)
  - Sick's Ranier Ale, 1965 (Folder 46.0)
  - Stemaier Beer, 1958 (Folder 47.0)
  - Stroh's, 1959, 1961 (Folder 48.0)
  - Utica Club, 1962-63 (Folder 49.0)
  - Waldech Beer, 1965 (Folder 50.0)
- Cigarettes, Cigars and Tobacco, 1957-68; 64 items
  - Camel, 1963-65 (Box 18, Folder 1.0)
  - Chesterfield, 1965 (Folder 2.0)
  - Chesterfield Kings, 1963 (Folder 3.0)
  - Days Word Chewing Tobacco, undated (Folder 4.0)
  - Duke, 1959 (Folder 5.0)
  - Dutch Masters Consolidated Cigar Co., 1957-58 (Folder 6.0)
  - Half & Half Pipe Tobacco, 1960 (Folder 7.0)
  - Hit Parade, 1957 (Folder 8.0)
  - Kent, 1957, 1959-60, 1963, 1965 (Folder 9.0)
  - Lark, 1965 (Folder 10.0)
  - L&M (Ligget & Myers), 1963 (Folder 11.0)
  - Lucky Strike, 1963-64 (Folder 12.0)
  - Marlboro, 1956-57 (Folder 13.0)
  - Mayfield, 1958 (Folder 14.0)
  - Muriel Cigars, 1963 (Folder 15.0)
  - Newport, 1957-63, 1965 (Folder 16.0)
  - Old Gold, 1957, 1965 (Folder 17.0)
  - Pall Mall, 1958-59, 1962, 1964, 1967 (Folder 18.0)
  - Parliament, 1957, 1959 (Folder 19.0)
  - Phillip Morris, 1957 (Folder 20.0)
  - Regent, 1956 (Folder 21.0)
  - Salem, 1962-63, 1965, 1968 (Folder 22.0)
  - Tarryton, 1957, 1959, 1964 (Folder 23.0)
  - Tempo, 1963 (Folder 24.0)
  - Viceroy, 1960 (Folder 25.0)
  - White Owl Cigars, 1958 (Folder 26.0)
  - Winston, 1957, 1959-60, 1962, 1964-65 (Folder 27.0)
  - York, 1961-62 (Folder 28.0)
- Drugs/Cosmetics, 1955-1966; 79 items
  - Baby Products/Tissues, 1955-61
    - Ammens Medicated Powder, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1.0)
    - Johnson & Johnson Baby Powder, 1961 (Folder 2.0)
    - Johnson & Johnson Baby Shampoo, 1955 (Folder 3.0)
    - Q-Tips, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Scott Tissue, undated (Folder 5.0)
    - Vanity Fair Tissues, 1957 (Folder 6.0)
    - Waldorf Tissue, 1956 (Folder 7.0)
  - Cold Medicines, 1957-64
    - Beech Nut Cough Drops, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 1.0)
    - Candettes Cough Drops, 1958 (Folder 2.0)
    - Cocilana Cough Nips, 1959 (Folder 3.0)
    - Coldene Cold Tablets and Liquid, 1959 (Folder 4.0)
    - Contac Cold Medicine, 1967 (Folder 5.0)
    - Creomulsion Cold Medicine, 1959, 1961 (Folder 6.0)
    - Medigum, 1958 (Folder 7.0)
    - Pine Brothers Cough Drops, 1964 (Folder 8.0)
    - Smith Brothers Cough Drops, 1957 (Folder 9.0)
    - Vicks Chemical Company Cough Drops, 1957-58, 1960-62 (Folder 10.0)
  - Deodorants, 1958-64
    - Manpower Deodorant, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1.0)
    - Mennen Spray and Push Button, 1962 (Folder 2.0)
    - Mum Deodorant, 1958 (Folder 3.0)
    - Old Spice, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Sutton Stick, undated (Folder 5.0)
    - Trig Roll-On, 1959 (Folder 6.0)
  - Men's Products, 1956-64
    - Barbasol Shaving Cream, 1957-58, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1.0)
    - Mennen Skin Bracer Aftershave, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - Mennen Sof't Stroke Shave Cream, 1960-61 (Folder 3.0)
    - Mennen Sof't Stroke Shave Cream & Push Button Deodorant, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
    - Noxzema Medicated Shave Cream, 1957 (Folder 5.0)
    - Old Spice After Shave, undated (Folder 6.0)
    - Old Spice Hair Groom Tonic, undated (Folder 7.0)
    - Old Spice Shampoo, undated (Folder 8.0)
    - Palmolive Shave Cream, 1958 (Folder 9.0)
    - Prince Matchabelli/Seaforth (Cologne Gift Sets), 1958 (Folder 10.0)
    - Shick Hot Lather Shave Cream, undated (Folder 11.0)
    - Shick Stainless Steel Razor Blades, undated (Folder 12.0)
    - Vaseline Hair Tonic, 1959 (Folder 13.0)
    - Vitalis Hair Cream, 1956-57 (Folder 14.0)
    - Zizanie de Fragonard Cologne, undated (Folder 15.0)
  - Suntan Lotion, 1959-63
    - Bain de Soleil Suntan Lotion, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1.0)
    - Bronzetan Suntan Lotion, undated (Folder 2.0)
    - Revlon Sunbath Suntan Lotion, 1961 (Folder 3.0)
    - Sea & Ski Suntan Lotion, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
  - Dental, 1956-66
    - Colgate Dental Cream, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1.0)
    - MacLean's, 1965-66 (Folder 2.0)
    - Pepsodent, 1956 (Folder 3.0)
    - Ultra Brite, undated (Folder 4.0)
  - Women's Products, 1957-64
    - Arpege Perfume (Mother's Day spots), 1964 (Box 25, Folder 1.0)
    - Avon Cosmetics, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - Breck Hair Set Mist, 1957 (Folder 3.0)
    - Clearasil (Feel Pretty Campaign), 1963 (Folder 4.0)
    - Colgate-Palmolive Hair Shampoo, 1963 (Folder 5.0)
    - Evening in Paris Bath Oil, 1962 (Folder 6.0)
    - Lanvin Arpege Perfume, 1963 (Folder 7.0)
    - Lanvin Arpege/My Skin Perfume, 1963 (Folder 8.0)
    - Noxzema Cover Girl, 1963 (Folder 9.0)
    - Noxzema Cover Girl Matte Makeup, 1962 (Folder 10.0)
    - Ting Medicated Cream, 1959 (Folder 11.0)
  - Over-the-Counter Remedies, 1957-64
    - Absorbine, Jr., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1.0)
    - Alka-Seltzer, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
    - Aspro Aspirin, 1958 (Folder 3.0)
    - Bromo Quinine, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Bufferin, 1958 (Folder 5.0)
    - Compoz, 1962-63 (Folder 6.0)
    - ENO, 1957 (Folder 7.0)
    - Ex-Lax, 1957, 1963 (Folder 8.0)
    - Feenamint, 1959 (Folder 9.0)
    - Johnson's Back Plasters, feat. Bob & Ray, 1957 (Folder 10.0)
    - Tums Antacid, 1958 (Folder 11.0)
- Farm Products, 1958-63; 13 items
  - Machinery, 1958-63
    - Case Tractors, null (Box 27, Folder 1.0)
    - Ford Tractors, 1961 (Folder 2.0)
    - International Harvester, 1958, 1960 (Folder 3.0)
    - Massey-Ferguson Tractors, 1962-63 (Folder 4.0)
    - McCullogh Chainsaws, 1960 (Folder 5.0)
    - Moline Farm Machines, 1959 (Folder 6.0)
    - Oliver Farm Machinery, 1958 (Folder 7.0)
  - Fertilizer, 1958-63
    - Armour Agricultural Chemical Company, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1.0)
    - Chilean Nitrate, 1961 (Folder 2.0)
    - Pacific Guano, 1958 (Folder 3.0)
    - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
- Food, 1955-64; 194 items
  - Bread, 1957-63
    - Arnold Bread, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 1.0)
    - Bond Bread, 1957 (Folder 2.0)
    - Cook Book Bread, 1959 (Folder 3.0)
    - Dandee Bread, 1960-61 (Folder 4.0)
    - Harvest Bread, 1960-61 (Folder 5.0)
    - Levy's Bread, 1957 (Folder 6.0)
    - Lite Diet Bread, 1960-61 (Folder 7.0)
    - Merita Bread, 1963 (Folder 8.0)
    - Monk's Bread, 1960-61 (Folder 9.0)
    - Mr. Big Celo, 1960-61 (Folder 10.0)
    - Pepperidge Farm, 1957-58 (Folder 11.0)
    - Rite Diet, 1962 (Folder 12.0)
    - Southern Bakeries Co. (Southern Bread), 1958 (Folder 13.0)
    - Tastemaster, 1959 (Folder 14.0)
    - Taystee Bread, 1959 (Folder 15.0)
    - Tender-Cut, 1962-63 (Folder 16.0)
    - Tip-Top, 1957 (Folder 17.0)
    - Tip-Top Regular, 1960-61 (Folder 18.0)
    - Tip-Top Tender Twist, 1960-61 (Folder 19.0)
    - Town Talk Bread, 1961 (Folder 20.0)
    - Wonder Bread, undated (Folder 21.0)
  - Cakes & Cookies, 1956-63
    - Betty Crocker's Brownie Mix, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 1.0)
    - Cadbury Biscuits, 1961 (Folder 2.0)
    - Johnston Cookies, 1961 (Folder 3.0)
    - Mother's, 1957, 1959, 1961 (Folder 4.0)
    - Patty Cake Cookies, 1963 (Folder 5.0)
    - Ry-Krisp Crackers, 1959 (Folder 6.0)
    - Sara Lee, 1962 (Folder 7.0)
    - Sunshine Biscuits, 1956-57 (Folder 8.0)
  - Candy & Gum, 1957-63
    - Beech Nut Gum, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 1.0)
    - Barricini Chocolate, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 1.0)
    - Nestle, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - Sen Sen, 1957 (Folder 3.0)
    - Whitman's Chocolates, undated (Folder 4.0)
  - Desserts, 1964
    - Ambrosia Rice Pudding, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1.0)
    - Jell-O, undated (Folder 2.0)
    - Reddi-2-Wip, undated (Folder 3.0)
  - Snacks, 1958-63
    - Blue Bell Potato Chips, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1.0)
    - Laura Scudder's Potato Chips, undated (Folder 2.0)
    - Lays Potato Chips, 1959 (Folder 3.0)
    - Old London Snacks, 1963 (Folder 4.0)
  - Cereal, 1957-64
    - Carnation Instant Wheat, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1.0)
    - Kellogs Corn Flakes, 1964 (Folder 2.0)
    - Maltex, 1960 (Folder 3.0)
    - Malt-O-Meal, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Post Toasties Corn Flakes, 1959 (Folder 5.0)
    - Ralston Purina, 1957-1959, 1961, 1963 (Folder 6.0)
    - Wheatena, 1964 (Folder 7.0)
    - Zoom, 1962 (Folder 8.0)
  - Coffee, 1955-64
    - Beech-Nut, 1960-61 (Box 36, Folder 1.0)
    - Borden's, 1957-59 (Folder 2.0)
    - Butter-Nut Coffee, 1959, 1961, 1963-64 (Folder 3.0)
    - Cain's, 1959 (Folder 4.0)
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1962-63 (Folder 5.0)
    - Chock Full O' Nuts, 1957, 1961 (Folder 6.0)
    - G. Washington, 1955-56 (Folder 7.0)
    - Hills Brothers, 1955, 1957 (Folder 8.0)
    - Jomar Instant Coffee, 1957 (Folder 9.0)
    - MJB, undated (Folder 10.0)
    - Nash's, 1961 (Folder 11.0)
    - Nescafe, 1957 (Folder 12.0)
    - Decafe (Nestle), 1957 (Folder 13.0)
    - Pan American, 1959 (Folder 14.0)
    - Savarin, 1958-59, 1961-62 (Folder 15.0)
    - Spartan, 1959 (Folder 16.0)
  - Dairy, 1959-64
    - Borden's Ice Cream, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 1.0)
    - Borden's Ready Diet, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
    - Breakstone Cottage Cheese, 1959 (Folder 3.0)
    - Breakstone Yogurt, 1961 (Folder 4.0)
    - Bridgeman Creameries, undated (Folder 5.0)
    - Carnation Evaporated Milk, 1964 (Folder 6.0)
    - Carnation Evaporated Milk (Spanish), 1964 (Folder 7.0)
    - Catawba Dairy, Inc., 1960 (Folder 8.0)
    - Dannon Yogurt, 1961, 1964 (Folder 9.0)
    - Deans Milk, undated (Folder 10.0)
    - Eskimo Pie, undated (Folder 11.0)
    - Jerseymaid Milk, undated (Folder 12.0)
    - Marin-Dell Dairy Foods, 1962 (Folder 13.0)
    - Meadow Gold Dairy Products, 1961 (Folder 14.0)
    - Milnot Milk Components, 1960 (Folder 15.0)
    - Montgomery Dairy Products, 1960 (Folder 16.0)
    - Nulaid Eggs, 1960 (Folder 17.0)
    - Rowan Dairy, 1960 (Folder 18.0)
    - Sealtest, undated (Folder 19.0)
    - West End Dairy, 1960 (Folder 20.0)
  - Fruits & Juices, 1960-65
    - Campbell's V-8 Juice, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 1.0)
    - Libby Tomato Juice, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - Mott, 1963-64 (Folder 3.0)
    - Ocean Spray Cranberry Juice, 1965 (Folder 4.0)
    - Real Gold Orange Base, 1960 (Folder 5.0)
    - Sacramento Tomato Juice, undated (Folder 6.0)
    - Seneca Grape Juice, 1964 (Folder 7.0)
    - Snap-E-Tom Tomato Drink, 1964 (Folder 8.0)
  - Fish & Seafood, 1956-63
    - Bird's Eye, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 1.0)
    - Coldwater, 1963 (Folder 2.0)
    - Starkist, 1961 (Folder 3.0)
  - Meats, 1957-61
    - American Lamb Council, undated (Box 40, Folder 1.0)
    - Ferris Bacon, 1957 (Folder 2.0)
    - Ferris Ham, 1957 (Folder 3.0)
    - Hygrade Food Products, 1959 (Folder 4.0)
    - Sperry's Homestead, 1961 (Folder 5.0)
  - Processed Meat Products, 1957-65
    - Nat Buring Packing Company, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 1.0)
    - Esskay, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
    - Pureta Franks, undated (Folder 3.0)
    - Vienna Sausage (Wilnot's), 1965 (Folder 4.0)
    - Williams' Fryer's Ham Salad, 1957 (Folder 5.0)
  - Rice, Pasta & Sauces, 1958-63
    - Carolina Rice, undated (Box 42, Folder 1.0)